Citizens Environmental Coalition; Records apap197
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Fundraising, 1985-2004; 3; 2.0 cubic ft.
  - Canvassing, Weekly Reports, 1993 (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 4)
  - Canvassing, Weekly Reports, 1994 (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 5)
  - Citizen's Clearinghouse for Hazardous Waste/ Community Leadership Development Grant Program, 1989-1993 (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 6)
  - Citizen's Clearinghouse for Hazardous Waste/ Community Leadership Development Grant Program, 1994 (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 7)
  - Citizen's Clearinghouse for Hazardous Waste/ Community Leadership Development Grant Program, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 8)
  - Citizen's Clearinghouse for Hazardous Waste/ Community Leadership Development Grant Program, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 9)
  - CEC Fundraising Documents, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 10)
  - Charles Stewart Mott Foundation, 1986-1991 (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 11)
  - Charles Stewart Mott Foundation, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 12)
  - Charles Stewart Mott Foundation, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 13)
  - Charles Stewart Mott Foundation, 1993 (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 14)
  - Charles Stewart Mott Foundation, 1994 (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 15)
  - Charles Stewart Mott Foundation, 1995-1997 (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 16)
  - Daily Canvassing Crew Statistics, Sampling, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 17)
  - Daily Canvassing Crew Statistics, Sampling, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 18)
  - ESC Training Grants, 1995-1999 (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 19)
  - ESC Training Grants, 2000-2004 (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 20)
  - Fundraising Contacts, 2002 (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 21)
  - Grants and Fundraising Information, 2000; 2002 (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 22)
  - James. C. Penney Fundraising, 1987-1992 (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 23)
  - Major Donor Campaign, 2000; 2 folders (Box 1 (3-Fundraising), Folder 24-25)
  - Major Donor Tracking, 2001; 5 folders (Box 2 (3-Fundraising), Folder 1-5)
  - North Shore Unitarian Universalist Veatch Program, 1985-1989 (Box 2 (3-Fundraising), Folder 6)
  - North Shore Unitarian Universalist Veatch Program, 1991-1994 (Box 2 (3-Fundraising), Folder 7)
  - Public Welfare Foundation, 1986-1989 (Box 2 (3-Fundraising), Folder 8)
  - Public Welfare Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (3-Fundraising), Folder 9)
  - Public Welfare Foundation, 1992-1994 (Box 2 (3-Fundraising), Folder 10)
  - Public Welfare Foundation, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (3-Fundraising), Folder 11)
  - Public Welfare Foundation, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (3-Fundraising), Folder 12)
  - Robert Sterling Clark Foundation, 1985-1988 (Box 2 (3-Fundraising), Folder 13)
  - Robert Sterling Clark Foundation, 1989-1997 (Box 2 (3-Fundraising), Folder 14)
  - W. Alton Jones Foundation, 1986-1989 (Box 2 (3-Fundraising), Folder 15)
  - W. Alton Jones Foundation, 1990-1994 (Box 2 (3-Fundraising), Folder 16)
- Graphics Files, 1977-2001; 4; 2.0 cubic ft.
  The records in this series consist of posters, artwork, photographs, and copies of cartoons and illustrations collected by CEC that depict environmental issues.
  - Artwork, ca. 1995-2000; 4.1
  - Cartoons, 1977-2000; 4.2; 1.0 cubic ft.
    This subseries contains political cartoons and comic strips pertaining to environmental issues that interested CEC. Most of these materials are copyrighted works.
    - Acid Rain, Cartoons, ca. 1982; 1985 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 1)
    - Air, Cartoons, ca. 1987; 1992; 1995 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 2)
    - Birds, Cartoons, ca. 1985 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 3)
    - Cartoons, etc., ca. 1988-1992 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 4)
    - Fish, Whales, etc., Water Species, Cartoons, ca. 1985 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 5)
    - Global Warming, Cartoons, ca. 1985 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 6)
    - Graphics, Cartoons, ca. 1986-1991 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 7)
    - Groundwater Poster Contest Winners, Cartoons, Undated (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 8)
    - Headings, Cartoons, ca. 1990 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 9)
    - Kids' Cartoons, ca. 1994 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 10)
    - Labor, Cartoons, ca. 1993 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, Cartoons, ca. 1989; 1993; 1995 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 12)
    - Nuclear Energy, Cartoons, ca. 1989; 1992; 2000 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 13)
    - People, Cartoons, ca. 1999 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 14)
    - Pesticides, Cartoons, ca. 1995; 1999-2000 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 15)
    - Sceneries, Cartoons, ca. 1985; 1994-1995 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 16)
    - Solid Waste, Cartoons, ca. 1992; 1994 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 17)
    - Toxic Cartoons, ca. 1977; 1986-1988; 1994; 1998 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 18)
    - Toxic Waste, Drums, Cartoons, ca. 1991 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 19)
    - Toxic Waste, Worldview, Cartoons, ca. 1985; 1988; 1998; 2000 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 20)
    - Water, Cartoons, ca. 1982; 1987; 1990; 2001 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 21)
    - Wildlife Conservation and Cartoons, ca. 1985 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 22)
  - Photographs, 1986-2001; 4.3; 1.0 cubic ft.
    The records in this subseries consist of photographs and negatives of CEC activities, members, and staff. Photographs, slides, and negatives relating to specific CEC causes can also be found in the Activities series.
    - Photographs, 1990 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 1)
      LEN Conference and LEN Syracuse Meetings, Photographs and Negatives.
    - Photographs, 1997 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 2)
      Diane Grelwater Classes, CHE Conference, Diane and Charlotte Awards, Akzo Building Solidarity Rally, Geneseo, CEC Award Winners at Earth Day Lobby Day, Fulton Landfill, Albion Ash Dump Hit.
    - Photographs, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 3)
      CEC/DWNY "Simpsons" and Don't Screw West Valley Press Event, Lobby Day Photo with Stacy Hammill, Beth and John Stouffer and Assistant, Hudson River Press Conference on Superfund Map with Edie and Clearwater, Governor Pataki; Fishing for Toxic Fish!.
    - Photographs, 1996 April (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 4)
      CEC, Earth Day Benefit, Photographs and Negatives.
    - Photographs, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 5)
      CEC 10th Anniversary Party Albany, October Canton Building Meeting May CHE Conference with CEC Award Winners (Tom and Anne).
    - Photographs, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 6)
      Staff Get Together, Greenpeace Practice at DH, Banner CEC, Fall Gloversville Building Meeting.
    - CEC Building and Strategic Planning, 1995 Spring (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 7)
    - Photographs, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 8)
      CEC Lockport Building Meeting, CEC Farmersville Building Meeting and Dump Tour.
    - LEN Conference, Albany, NY, 1995 October (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 9)
    - Photographs, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 10)
      Love Canal Mutant Pageant, State Capitol, Albany, with Lois Gibbs, Gary Michael, Diane Heminway, DWNY folks, etc.
    - Love Canal Rallies, 1991 Spring (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 11)
    - Photographs, 1986-1989 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 12)
      Award Winners CEC, Superfund Albany Press Conference, Niagara Falls Steering Committee Meeting, Toxics in Your Community Coalition, CEC group at DEC, Ward Stone Rally, CECOS Press Event, LEN Conference, EPL Conference with Toxics Coalition, Cold Springs Building Meeting.
    - LEN Conference, Albany, Photographs and Negatives, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 13)
    - Photographs, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 14)
      Diane at USWA Chemical Hazard Training in Costume, Banner, CEC C+D Meeting and Hinchey Award Presentation, Long Island Dump Tours, Elsa and Joan, Sonia Road Dump Pictures, CEC Staff Picture, Earth Day Lobby Day, Incineration Press Hit, CEC Mugs.
    - Photographs, 1996 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 15)
      CEC April Building Meeting, CEC January Building Meeting, Earth Day Lobby Day, Cayadulto Creek Bill Board.
    - CEC C+D Statewide Meeting, Photographs and Negatives, 1991 March 02 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 16)
    - Photographs, 1998 Spring (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 17)
      CEC Staff Pictures, Albany, Rally on Superfund/Corporate Welfare, Greenpeace Canada Dioxin Event, Rochester Kodak Press Conference.
    - LEN Conference, 1998 October (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 18)
    - LEN Conference, 1993 November (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 19)
    - LEN Conference, 1992; 2 folders (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 20-21)
    - Photographs, 1997 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 22)
      LEN and CEC, Laudis Plastics Rally, February 1, LEN Group Meeting, May 1997.
    - LEN Conference, Photographs and Negatives, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 23)
    - CEC LEN Conference, Negatives, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 24)
    - Toxic Tour, Schenectady, Photographs and Negatives, 2000 December 09 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 25)
    - Toxic Tours, Rensselaer - BASF, Schenectady - United Planting, Photographs and Negatives, 2000 December 09 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 26)
    - Caledonia Groundwater Workshop, 2000 November 15 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 27)
    - CEC Contact Sheets and Negatives, 1991; Undated (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 28)
    - CEC Photographs, Undated (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 29)
    - CEC Photographs and Photocopies, Undated (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 30)
    - CEC Photographs, 1990 April 19 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 31)
    - CEC Photographs, Undated (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 32)
    - LEN Conference, Photographs and Negatives, 2001 May 06 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 33)
    - LEN Carnival, Photographs and Negatives, 2001 May 07 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 34)
    - Photographs, 2000 October 12; 2000 October 30 (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 35)
      HCWH Conference, October 12, Hearing and Rally, October 30.
    - HCWH Meeting, Photographs and Negatives, 2000 December (Box 1 (4-Graphics Files), Folder 36)
- Issue Files, 1978-2002; 5; 10.73 cubic ft.
  This series contains information about environmental issues that interested CEC. CEC was not active in every environmental issue represented in this series. The records show that CEC collected information about environmental science, environmental problems and their solutions, and environmental movements in which they did not become involved. The records include reports, correspondence, guides, news clippings, publications, notes, and photographs. These files were collected by CEC and for the most part the folder titles have been preserved from the list that accompanied them (see Box 1 Folder 1).
  - CEC Issue File Lists, Undated (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 1)
  - "A Call to Establish a Catskill Mountain Green Party", Undated (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 2)
  - Above-ground Storage and Excavation, 1986-1996 (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 3)
  - "The Activist's Guide to Resources for Researching Corporations", ERIN, 1997 September (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 4)
  - Air Pollution, 1986-2001; 2 folders (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 5-6)
  - Air Toxics, 1985-1999; 2 folders (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 7-8)
  - Arsenic, 1997-2002 (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 9)
  - Asbestos, 1982-1997; 2 folders (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 10-11)
  - Assessment of the Potential Environmental Impact of Incinerator Emissions, 1991 (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 12)
  - Agency for Toxic Substances and Disease Registry (ATSDR), 1996-1998 (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 13)
  - Asthma, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 14)
  - Attorney General, 1993-2000 (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 15)
  - Batteries, 2002 (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 16)
  - Bill Drafting Manual, State of New York, 1985 (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 17)
  - "Biomonitoring to Achieve Control of Toxic Effluents", EPA, 1987 September (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 18)
  - Bioremediation Technology, 1987-1998; 2 folders (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 19-20)
  - Biotesting, 1988; 2002 (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 21)
  - Birth Defects, 1989-2001 (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 22)
  - Bond Act 1986, Environmental, 1986-1990 (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 23)
  - Bond Act 1996, Clean Water/Clean Air, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 24)
  - Bottled Water Studies, 1982-1991 (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 25)
  - BRC (Below Regulatory Concern), 1990-1992 (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 26)
  - Breast Cancer, 1991-1999 (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 27)
  - Browing Ferris Industries, Inc. (BFI), 1987-1999 (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 28)
  - Burn Barrels/Open Burning of Solid Waste, 1984-2002; 2 folders (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 29-30)
  - Business Council, 1999 (Box 1 (5-Issue Files), Folder 31)
  - Campaign Contribution Report, 1990 (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 1)
  - Cancer, 1996-1998 (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 2)
  - "Capacity Assurance Plan", NYS DEC, Division of Hazardous Substances Regulation, 1989 October 17 (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 3)
  - Cellular Microwave, 1996-2001; Undated (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 4)
  - Cement Kilns, 1987-1990 (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 5)
  - Cement Kilns, 1991-1996 (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 6)
  - Central New York Committee on Occupational Safety and Health, 1997 (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 7)
  - Chlorine, 1991; 1992-1994 (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 8)
  - Chlorine, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 9)
  - Chemical Sensitivity, 1989-1994; 1999-2001 (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 10)
  - Chemical Spills, 1987-1997; 1999 (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 11)
  - Children and Toxics, 1985-1986; 1995-1999 (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 12)
  - Children and Toxics, 2000 (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 13)
  - Children and Toxics, 2001-2002, Undated (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 14)
  - CIO Landfill, 1988-1994; Undated (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 15)
  - Citizen Participation, 1983; 1987; 1993-1994; Undated (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 16)
  - Citizen Participation Legislation, 1991-1994; Undated (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 17)
  - Citizen Participation Plans, Hazardous Waste Sites, 1983; 1986-1987 (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 18)
  - Citizen Participation Plans, Hazardous Waste Sites, 1988-1990 (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 19)
  - Citizen Participation Plans, Hazardous Waste Sites, 1992-1993; 1996-1998 (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 20)
  - Citizen Participation Plans, Hazardous Waste Sites, Undated (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 21)
  - Citizen Suits, 1994-1996 (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 22)
  - "The Citizens Toxics Protection Manual", Ch. I-V, 1988 (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 23)
  - "The Citizens Toxics Protection Manual", Ch. VI-VII, 1988 (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 24)
  - "The Citizens Toxics Protection Manual", Ch. VIII, 1988 (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 25)
  - "The Citizens Toxics Protection Manual", Ch. IX-XI, 1988 (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 26)
  - "The Citizens Toxics Protection Manual", Ch. XII-XIII, 1988 (Box 2 (5-Issue Files), Folder 27)
  - Clean Sites, 1984; 1990-1991 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 1)
  - Clean Water Act, 1992-1993; 1997; 2002 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 2)
  - Cleanup Levels, 1980; 1984; 1987-1991 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 3)
  - Cleanup Levels, 1994-2001; Undated (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 4)
  - Cleanup Levels, "Soil Screening Guidance", EPA, 1996 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 5)
  - Cleanup Levels, "Soil Screening Guidance", Appendixes, EPA, 1996 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 6)
  - Cleanup Levels, "Soil Screening Guidance", User's Guide, EPA, 1996 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 7)
  - Clear Air Act, 1990-1997 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 8)
  - Coal Mining, 1991; 1997 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 9)
  - Coal Plants, 1991; 1993-1996; 2000 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 10)
  - Coal Tar Sites, 1991 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 11)
  - Community Advisory Committees, 1992; 1995 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 12)
  - Community Organizing, 1994 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 13)
  - Composting, 1989-1998 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 14)
  - Computers/Video Display Terminals, 1989; 2002; Undated (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 15)
  - Construction and Demolition (C and D) Pollution, 1988-1998; 3 folders (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 16-18)
  - Corporate Research, 1992-1995; Undated (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 19)
  - Cost Benefit Analysis, 1995-1996 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 20)
  - "Crony Environmentalism", Bernardo Issel, Nonprofit Accountability Project, 1999 June (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 21)
  - DEET, 1991-1992; 1995; Undated (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 22)
  - DEC Commissioner, 1994-2001; Undated (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 23)
  - Department of Health Guidelines, 1983; 1987; 1992; 1997; 2002 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 24)
  - "Drinking Water...An Endangered Resource", CCHW, 1988 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 25)
  - Dioxins, 1986-1987; 1991-1995 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 26)
  - Dioxins, 1996-2000 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 27)
  - Dioxins, Undated (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 28)
  - Dioxins, Greenpeace Publications, 1994; 1997 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 29)
  - Du Pont, 1991 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 30)
  - Dry Cleaning, 1992; 1994-1996 (Box 3 (5-Issue Files), Folder 31)
  - Earth Day Lobby Day, 1995-1996; 1998-2002 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 1)
  - East Fishkill Mine Proposal, 1991-1997 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 2)
  - Electromagnetic Fields, 1987; 1988; 1990-1996 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 3)
  - Electromagnetic Fields, 1999-2001; Undated (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 4)
  - Enforcement, 1990-1997 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 5)
  - Enforcement, 1998-1999; Undated (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 6)
  - Enforcement, DEC Annual Reports, 1990-1992 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 7)
  - "Environment 2000", New York State, Mario Cuomo: Governor, 1986 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 8)
  - Environmental Enforcement/Audit Privilege, 1989-1996 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 9)
  - Environmental Education, 1989-1996 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 10)
  - Environmental Facilities Corporation, 1994 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 11)
  - Environmental Justice, 1988-1999 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 12)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1991-1993 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 13)
  - Environmental Risk Assessment, 1991-1993 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 14)
  - "Everyone's Backyard", 2000-2001 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 15)
  - Fiberglass - Health Effects, 1991-1996 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 16)
  - "Final Combined Regulatory Impact and Environmental Impact Statement: Title 6, Chapter X", NYSDEC, 1998 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 17)
  - Financial Disclosure, New York State Government, 1990-1994 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 18)
  - Fish Contamination, 1992-1998 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 19)
  - Fish Contamination, 1999-2001 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 20)
  - Fluoridation, 1994-2000 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 21)
  - Food Irradiation, 1988-1999 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 22)
  - Free Trade/NAFTA, 1991-1994 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 23)
  - Freedom of Information Act/Law, 1978-1996 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 24)
  - "From Poison to Prevention", The National Toxics Campaign Fund, 1989 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 25)
  - "From Pollution to Prevention: A progress Report on Waste Reduction", US Congress, Office of Technology Assessment, 1987 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 26)
  - General Electric, 1992-1997 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 27)
  - Good Neighbor Agreements, 1993-1996 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 28)
  - Great Lakes Water Quality, 1991-1999 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 29)
  - "Great Lakes Water Quality Agreement of 1978 (Revised)", 1987 (Box 4 (5-Issue Files), Folder 30)
  - Groundwater Contamination, 1984-1992 (Box 5 (5-Issue Files), Folder 1)
  - Groundwater Contamination, 1993-1994 (Box 5 (5-Issue Files), Folder 2)
  - Groundwater Contamination, 1995-1996 (Box 5 (5-Issue Files), Folder 3)
  - Groundwater Contamination, 1997 (Box 5 (5-Issue Files), Folder 4)
  - Groundwater Contamination, 1998-2002 (Box 5 (5-Issue Files), Folder 5)
  - Hazardous Waste Incineration, 1984-1991 (Box 5 (5-Issue Files), Folder 6)
  - Hazardous Waste Incineration, 1992 (Box 5 (5-Issue Files), Folder 7)
  - Hazardous Waste Incineration, 1993-1997 (Box 5 (5-Issue Files), Folder 8)
  - Hazardous Waste TAGMs, 1988-1990; 1992-1996 (Box 5 (5-Issue Files), Folder 9)
  - Hazardous Waste Technologies, 1986-1988; 1992; 1999 (Box 5 (5-Issue Files), Folder 10)
  - Hazardous Waste Technologies, 1982; 1986; 1988-1989; 1991-1993; 1995-1997 (Box 5 (5-Issue Files), Folder 11)
  - Hazardous Waste Technologies, DEC, 1987-1990 (Box 5 (5-Issue Files), Folder 12)
  - Hazardous Waste Technologies, EPA/Site, 1983; 1986-1989; 1992; 1995 (Box 5 (5-Issue Files), Folder 13)
  - Hazardous Waste-Transportation, US Dept. of Transportation, 1988-1992 (Box 5 (5-Issue Files), Folder 14)
  - Health Studies, 1995-1996; 1998-1999 (Box 5 (5-Issue Files), Folder 15)
  - Household Hazardous Waste, 1988-1992; 1994 (Box 5 (5-Issue Files), Folder 16)
  - The Hudson River, 1987 (Box 5 (5-Issue Files), Folder 17)
  - "In Harm's Way: Toxic Threats to Child Development", GBPSR, 2000 (Box 5 (5-Issue Files), Folder 18)
  - Incinerator Ash, 1987; 1990; 1992-1996; 2000 (Box 5 (5-Issue Files), Folder 19)
  - Incinerator Ash, 1987-1994 (Box 5 (5-Issue Files), Folder 20)
  - Indoor Air, 1988-1989; 1991-1993; 1995; 1999; 2001 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 1)
  - Industrial Waste, 1989; 1993 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 2)
  - Injection Wells, New York State, 1975 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 3)
  - Integrated Pest Management (IPM), Cornell Cooperative Extension, 2000-2003 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 4)
  - Integrated Waste Systems (IWS), 1983; 1991-1994; 1996-1997 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 5)
  - Jobs and Environment, 1992; 1995 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 6)
  - Kids Against Pollution, 1992; 1996-1997 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 7)
  - Landfill Problems, 1987; 1991-1994; 1996; 1999; 2002 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 8)
  - Landfill Problems, 1988; 1991-1993 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 9)
  - Lead, 1981; 1985-1991; 1994; 1998 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 10)
  - Lead, 1989-1992; 1995-1997; 2001-2002 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 11)
  - League of Conservative Voters, 1993; 1996-1999 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 12)
  - Legislative Districts, Maps, 1992 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 13)
  - Liability, 1993-1994; 1996-1999 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 14)
  - Libraries, 1995; 2000 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 15)
  - Lobby Day, 1996; 1998; 2000 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 16)
  - Lobbying, How To's, 1988; 1990; 1996 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 17)
  - Lobbying Commission, New York State, 1992; 2004 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 18)
  - Love Canal Anniversary, 1998 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 19)
  - Manure Spreading, 1993 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 20)
  - Mediation Examples, 1978; 1985-1988; 1992; 1996-1997; 1999 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 21)
  - Medical Waste, 1989-1990; 1992; 1997-1998 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 22)
  - Medical Waste, 1988-1994; 1996 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 23)
  - Medical Waste, Radioactive, 1988; 1992-1994 (Box 6 (5-Issue Files), Folder 24)
  - Medical Waste, Incineration, 1989-1991; 1994; 1996-1998 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 1)
  - Medical Waste, incineration, 1992; 1995 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 2)
  - Mercury, 1997-1999; 2001-2002 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 3)